Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
- College Files, Series IV
  - Taiwan
    - Soochow University
      - Proposals, 1976-1979 (Box 137, Folder 1924-1925)
      - Twanmoh, Joseph, 1973-1979 (Box 137, Folder 1926-1927)
    - Tunghai University
      - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1971-1975 (Box 137, Folder 1928)
      - University Cabinet Meeting - Minutes, 1971-1978 (Box 137, Folder 1929-1930)
      - About Tunghai, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 1931)
      - Aims and Purposes for Tunghai, 1965-1969 (Box 137, Folder 1932)
      - Alexander, Paul Lucy, 1971-1979 (Box 138, Folder 1933)
      - Alumni/Development Office, 1971-1979 (Box 138, Folder 1934-1935)
      - Architecture Department [see also: Han Pao Teh], 1971-1976 (Box 138, Folder 1936)
      - Asian Ecological Society, 1976-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1937)
      - Biology Department, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 1938)
      - Blackiston, Lewis, 1971-1976
      - Board of Directors, 1972-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1939)
      - Briggs, Sara, 1974-1977 (Box 138, Folder 1940)
      - Budget - Grants, 1971-1973 (Box 138, Folder 1941)
      - Building (Box 138, Folder 1942)
      - Fine Arts, 1971-1973
      - Projects, 1972
      - C - General, 1977-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1943)
      - Calhoun, Wanda [see: Library Report]
      - Cha, Liang-chien, 1972-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1944)
      - Chan, Kenneth, 1975
      - Chang, Chi-jen, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 1945)
      - Chang, Chi-ming, 1973
      - Chang, Eugene Yu-sheng Shirley, 1973-1978 (Box 138, Folder 1946)
      - Chang, Liu-sheng Olivia, 1972-1974 (Box 138, Folder 1947)
      - Chao, Ching-hsi, 1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 1948)
      - Chaplains, 1971-1973
      - Chemistry Department, 1973-1977 (Box 138, Folder 1949)
      - Chen, Hsien-fang, 1971-1977 (Box 138, Folder 1950)
      - Chen, Yu-chung, 1971-1976
      - Cheng, Ten An (Andrew), 1971-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1951)
      - Chinese Culture and Christianity, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 1952)
      - Chuang, John (Chi-an), 1976-1978
      - Commencements, 1972-1975 (Box 139, Folder 1953)
      - Controller, Office of, 1972-1973
      - Counseling Center, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 1954)
      - Church Architecture Project, 1976-1977 (Box 139, Folder 1955)
      - Diplomas, n.d. (Box 139, Folder 1956)
      - Dupler, Dorothy, 1975-1977 (Box 139, Folder 1957)
      - E - General (Box 139, Folder 1958)
      - Edwards, Norman, 1978
      - Endowment Fund, 1969-1978 (Box 139, Folder 1959)
      - Endowment Fund - Alumni Chair, 1973-1977 (Box 139, Folder 1960)
      - Environmental Research Center, 1971-1979 (Box 139, Folder 1961-1962)
      - Environmental Studies, Asian Institute of, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 1963)
      - Environmental Studies Building, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 1964)
      - Environmental Research - Taiwan Squirrel Study, 1974-1975 (Box 140, Folder 1965)
      - Eu, Hunter, 1971 (Box 140, Folder 1966)
      - F - General
      - Faculty and Staff Lists, 1971-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1967)
      - Faculty Council, 1971-1972 (Box 140, Folder 1968)
      - Faculty Development Fellowships, 1971-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1969)
      - Faculty Salaries, 1971-1973 (Box 140, Folder 1970)
      - Faculty and Staff Correspondence, 1971-1972
      - Farm - Experimental, 1973-1974 (Box 140, Folder 1971)
      - Fikes, Lewis, 1971-1975 (Box 140, Folder 1972)
      - Finance
      - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 140, Folder 1973)
      - Budget Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 140, Folder 1974)
      - Proposals - General, 1974-1975
      - Quarterly Statements, 1971-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1975)
      - Five-Year Plan, 1970-1973 (Box 140, Folder 1976)
      - Founder's Day, 1959
      - Franks, Jesse, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 1977)
      - Fung, Hu-Hsiang, 1977-1979
      - General Education, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 1978)
      - Guerrant, Mary T., 1976
      - Han, Pao Teh, 1971-1977 (Box 140, Folder 1979-1980)
      - Harvard-Yenching Oberlin Research Grants, 1971-1977 (Box 140, Folder 1981)
      - History, 1951-1959, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 1982)
      - Housing - General, 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 1983)
      - Hsiao, Chi-tzung, 1971-1974
      - Hsieh, Ming San, 1972-1978 (Box 141, Folder 1984-1986)
      - Hsieh, Wan-chen, 1973-1976 (Box 141, Folder 1987)
      - Hsu, Stephen, c. 1977 (Box 141, Folder 1988)
      - Humanities Center, 1973-1975
      - Hwai En School, 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1989)
      - Industrial Engineering Dept., 1968-1975
      - Information, 1964-1973 (Box 141, Folder 1990)
      - Institute of Chinese Literature/Institute of History, Graduate, 1969-1973 (Box 141, Folder 1991)
      - K - General, 1972-1979 (Box 141, Folder 1992)
      - Kang, Dolores, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 1993)
      - Kao, Chao-jen (Julian), 1971-1973
      - Kao, S. C., 1971-1977 (Box 141, Folder 1994)
      - Kiang, Yu-lung, 1971-1977 (Box 141, Folder 1995)
      - Ku, Tung-chou and I-ching, 1971-1973
      - Kuo, Albert T. Y., 1973-1979 (Box 141, Folder 1996)
      - L - General (Box 141, Folder 1997)
      - Laale, Hans W., 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1998)
      - Language Laboratory, 1971-1973
      - Li, Wen Lang [see: Environmental Research Center]
      - Library, 1971-1979 (Box 141, Folder 1999)
      - Library Report, 1971
      - Lin, Sen-yuan (Maurice), 1970-1972 (Box 142, Folder 2000)
      - Lin, Pin-yao, 1972 (Box 142, Folder 2001)
      - Lin, Sheng-hsiung, 1972-1974
      - Liu, Felix, 1973-1974 (Box 142, Folder 2002)
      - Lu, Shih-peng, 1971-1975 (Box 142, Folder 2003)
      - Luce Chapel, 1971-1974 (Box 142, Folder 2004)
      - Luce Chair of Philosophy and Religion, 1964-1965, 1971-1975
      - Manno, Mark, 1976-1979 (Box 142, Folder 2005)
      - Mei, Ko-wang, 1972-1979 (Box 142, Folder 2005-2006)
      - Music Department, 1971-1976 (Box 142, Folder 2007)
      - Oberlin in Taiwan, 1971-1973 (Box 142, Folder 2008)
      - Overseas Personnel, 1964-1979 (Box 142, Folder 2009)
      - Pan Library (Pan, T. K.), 1975-1979 (Box 142, Folder 2010)
      - Pangilinan, Crispin P., Jr., 1972-1978 (Box 142, Folder 2011)
      - Patterson, Robert G., 1964-1978 (Box 142, Folder 2012)
      - Philosophy Department [see: Fung, Hu-hsiang]
      - Physics Program, 1974 (Box 143, Folder 2013)
      - President - Reports of, 1974 (Box 143, Folder 2014)
      - Proposals, Grants, Loans, 1975-1980 (Box 143, Folder 2015-2018)
      - Project Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 143, Folder 2019)
      - Purchasing and Shipments - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 144, Folder 2020)
      - Questionnaire, 1977
      - Rose, Juanelva, 1971-1979 (Box 144, Folder 2021)
      - Rural Community Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 144, Folder 2022)
      - Scholarships, 1971-1980
      - Seal of Tunghai University, 1958-1963 (Box 144, Folder 2023)
      - Seng, Harris B. H., 1971 (Box 144, Folder 2024)
      - Senner, Edward L., 1977
      - Shepard, Ivor, 1973-1977
      - Statistics, 1971-1973 (Box 144, Folder 2025)
      - Survey Report, 1964 (Box 144, Folder 2026)
      - Sun, Wesley K. C., 1971-1973 (Box 144, Folder 2027)
      - T - General
      - Tu, Hengtse, 1971-1978 (Box 144, Folder 2028)
      - Tang, Shou-chien, 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 2029)
      - Tsai, Chi-ching, 1971-1972 (Box 144, Folder 2030)
      - W - General (Box 144, Folder 2031)
      - Walter, Gary (personal), 1971-1977 (Box 144, Folder 2032)
      - Wang, Gene Tang, 1971-1973 (Box 144, Folder 2033)
      - Wang, Yuan-tseng [see: Controller, Office of]
      - Water System, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 2033)
      - "What is the United Board?" - Chinese Translation, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 2034)
      - Wu, Ying-keh, 1973
      - X-Y-Z - General (Box 144, Folder 2035)
  - Thailand
    - Payap College
      - A.S.H.A. Application Proposal, 1976 (Box 144, Folder 2036)
      - Boonthong Poocharoen, 1974-1979 (Box 145, Folder 2037)
      - Consultations, 1978 (Box 145, Folder 2038)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 145, Folder 2039-2040)
      - Kingshill, Konrad, 1975-1979 (Box 145, Folder 2041)
      - Library, 1979 (Box 145, Folder 2042)
      - Overseas List, 1975-1979
      - Progress Reports, 1977 (Box 145, Folder 2043)
      - Proposals, Grants, Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 145, Folder 2044)
      - Tapingkae, Amnuay, 1974-1979 (Box 145, Folder 2045)
- Audio-visual Materials, Series V
  - Photographs
    - General
      - ACUCA and CACHEA (Box 146, Folder 2046)
      - Archives #1 (Box 146, Folder 2047)
      - Archives #2 (Box 146, Folder 2048)
      - Asian Countries (Box 146, Folder 2049)
      - Beth Moore - Retirement Dinner 1976 (Box 146, Folder 2050)
      - China - Seals of Universities (Box 146, Folder 2051)
      - College/University Seals - Negatives (Box 146, Folder 2052)
      - Committees, Area - United Board (Box 146, Folder 2053)
      - Dansalan Research Centre (Box 146, Folder 2054)
      - Faculty Conferences (Box 146, Folder 2055)
      - Fellows Conferences (Box 146, Folder 2056)
      - Fenn Testimonial 1970 (Box 146, Folder 2057)
      - Orphanages and Hospitals (Box 146, Folder 2058)
      - Presidents' Conferences (Box 146, Folder 2059)
      - Presidents' Visit to USA - 1966 (Box 147, Folder 2060)
      - Singapore - Malaysia Student Christian Center (Box 147, Folder 2061)
      - Staff (Box 147, Folder 2062)
      - Trustees/Counselors (Box 147, Folder 2063)
      - Trustee Meetings #1 1976-1978 (Box 147, Folder 2064)
      - Trustee Meetings #2 1979-1980 (Box 147, Folder 2065)
      - Trustee Meetings #3 1981-1984 (Box 147, Folder 2066)
      - Trustee Meetings #4 1985-1987 (Box 147, Folder 2067)
      - United Board's 50th Anniversary (Box 147, Folder 2068)
      - United Board's 50th Anniversary - Negatives and Duplicates (Box 148, Folder 2069)
      - United Board's Tour - Casilda, Luzares (Box 148, Folder 2070)
      - United Board's Tour - 1969 - China (Box 148, Folder 2071)
      - United Board Tour 1979 - China #1 - S. Schriver (PTL) (Box 148, Folder 2072)
      - United Board Tour 1979 - China #1 (cont.) - S. Schriver (Box 148, Folder 2073)
      - United Board Tour 1979 - China #2 (Box 148, Folder 2074)
      - United Board Tour 1979 - China #2 -PTL with S. Schriver (Box 148, Folder 2075)
      - United Board Tour 1980-1981 - China (Box 148, Folder 2076)
      - Vellore Conference - 1983 (Box 148, Folder 2077)
      - Western Personnel - Wanda Calhoun and Carey (Box 148, Folder 2078)
      - Workshops (Box 148, Folder 2079)
      - Yu, Timothy (Box 148, Folder 2080)
      - Yunnan Institute of Nationalities (Box 148, Folder 2081)
      - Unidentified pictures (Box 148, Folder 2082)
    - China
      - Fujian Teachers University (Box 149, Folder 2083)
      - Hwa Nan Professional College and Hua Kiao University (Box 149, Folder 2084)
      - South China Normal University and East China Normal University (Box 149, Folder 2085)
      - Sichuan University (Box 149, Folder 2086)
      - Shaanxi Teachers University, Xian (Box 149, Folder 2087)
      - Shaanxi University (Box 149, Folder 2088)
      - SouthWest China Teachers College (Box 149, Folder 2089)
      - Xiamen University (Box 149, Folder 2090)
    - Hong Kong
      - Chung Chi College (Box 149, Folder 2091)
      - Chung Chi College (cont.) (Box 149, Folder 2092)
      - Chung Chi College (cont.) (Box 149, Folder 2093)
      - Hong Kong Baptist College (Box 149, Folder 2094)
      - Hong Kong Baptist College (cont.) (Box 149, Folder 2095)
    - India
      - India (Box 150, Folder 2096)
    - Indonesia
      - Nommensen University, Sumatra (Box 150, Folder 2097)
      - Petra Christian University (1) (Box 150, Folder 2098)
      - Petra Christian University (2) (Box 150, Folder 2099)
      - Petra Christian University (3) (Box 150, Folder 2100)
      - Universitas Kristen (Box 150, Folder 2101)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (1) (Box 150, Folder 2102)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (1) (Box 150, Folder 2103)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (1) (Box 150, Folder 2104)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (2) (Box 151, Folder 2105)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (2) (Box 151, Folder 2106)
      - Satya Wacana Christian University (2) (Box 151, Folder 2107)
    - Japan
      - International Christian University (Box 151, Folder 2108)
      - Sophia University (Box 151, Folder 2109)
    - Korea
      - Ewha Woman's University (Box 152, Folder 2110)
      - Soong Jun University (Box 152, Folder 2111)
      - Yonsei University - October 1972 (Box 152, Folder 2112)
      - Yonsei University Book 1 (Box 152, Folder 2113)
      - Yonsei University Book 1 (cont.) (Box 152, Folder 2114)
      - Yonsei University Book 1 (cont.) (Box 152, Folder 2115)
      - Yonsei University Book 2 (Box 153, Folder 2116)
      - Yonsei University Book 2 (cont.) (Box 153, Folder 2117)
      - Yonsei University Book 2 (cont.) (Box 153, Folder 2118)
      - Yonsei University Book 3 (Box 153, Folder 2119)
      - Yonsei University Book 3 (Box 153, Folder 2120)
    - Philippines
      - Central Philippine University (Box 154, Folder 2121)
      - De la Salle University (Box 154, Folder 2122)
      - Northern Christian University (Box 154, Folder 2123)
      - Philippine Christian University (Box 154, Folder 2124)
      - Philippine Christian University (cont.) (Box 154, Folder 2125)
      - Silliman - Smythes' Memorabilia (Box 154, Folder 2126)
      - Silliman University (Box 154, Folder 2127)
      - Silliman University (cont.) (Box 154, Folder 2128)
      - Silliman University Book 1 (Box 155, Folder 2129)
      - Silliman University Book 1 (cont.) (Box 155, Folder 2130)
      - Silliman University Book 2 (Box 155, Folder 2131)
      - Silliman University Book 2 (cont.) (Box 155, Folder 2132)
      - Silliman University Book 3 (Box 155, Folder 2133)
      - Silliman University Book 3 (cont.) (Box 155, Folder 2134)
      - Silliman University Book 4 (Box 156, Folder 2135)
      - Silliman University Book 4 (cont.) (Box 156, Folder 2136)
      - Southern Christian University (Box 156, Folder 2137)
      - Trinity College of Quezon City (Box 156, Folder 2138)
      - Xavier University (Box 156, Folder 2139)
    - Taiwan
      - Soochow University (Box 156, Folder 2140)
      - Tunghai University (Box 156, Folder 2141)
      - Tunghai University (cont.) (Box 156, Folder 2142)
      - Tunghai University Book 1 (Box 157, Folder 2143)
      - Tunghai University Book 1 (cont.) (Box 157, Folder 2144)
      - Tunghai University Book 1 (cont.) (Box 157, Folder 2145)
      - Tunghai University Book 2 (Box 157, Folder 2146)
      - Tunghai University Book 2 (cont.) (Box 157, Folder 2147)
      - Tunghai University Book 2 (cont.) (Box 157, Folder 2148)
    - Thailand
      - Payap College (Box 157, Folder 2149)
      - Payap College (cont.) (Box 157, Folder 2150)
  - Slides and Films
    - General - United Board Events (Box 158, Folder 2151)
    - 16 mm film on Satya Wacana
    - 3 regular film strips
    - one audiotape - China Today
    - Hong Kong - Chung Chi College (Box 159, Folder 2152)
    - Indonesia - Satya Wacana University (Box 159, Folder 2153)
    - India
    - Korea - Yonsei University - Book 1 (Box 159, Folder 2154)
    - Korea - Yonsei University - Book 2 (Box 159, Folder 2155)
    - Philippines - Silliman University - Book 1 (Box 160, Folder 2156)
    - Philippines - Silliman University - Book 2 (Box 160, Folder 2157)
    - Philippines - Silliman University - Book 3 (Box 160, Folder 2158)
    - Taiwan - Soochow University (Box 160, Folder 2159)
    - Taiwan - Tunghai University (Box 160, Folder 2160)
    - Boxes with slides on:- Chung Chi College, Korea, Silliman University (duplicates), Tunghai (three boxes), Tunghai (duplicates), Yonsei (duplicates) (Box 161)
    - Silliman University (2/16mm films) (Box Ov1)
    - Silliman University (1/16mm film); Unidentified1/16mm film (Box Ov2)
    - 16mm film on:Yonsei University - Seoul-Korea 1982; Yonsei Choir - Lincoln Centre; Yonsei Medical Centre - 1972 (Box Ov3)